webcams.com 2017-09-30

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                       PRIVACY POLICY
         Last Modified: April 25, 2017
Introduction
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with
this privacy policy.
This privacy policy describes the types of information we may collect from the users or
the performers or that you may provide when you visit www.mydirtyhobby.com
(hereinafter “MyDirtyHobby” or the “Website”), our practices for collecting, using,
maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information and your choices about such uses
and disclosures.
We encourage you to read this privacy policy carefully when visiting our Website. By
using our Website, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this
privacy policy for information on how to contact us.
This privacy policy applies to information we collect:
               on this Website,
               in e-mail, text and other communications between you and this Website,
               through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website,
                which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and
                this Website, or
               when you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party
                websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to
                this policy.
It does not apply to information collected by:
               us offline or through any other means, including on any other website
                operated by us or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries);
                or
               any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through
                any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be
                accessible from or on the Website.
Please read this privacy policy carefully to understand our policies and practices
regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies
and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using the Website,
or by clicking to accept or agree to the Terms of Service or the Terms of Use when this
option is made available to you, you agree to this privacy policy. This privacy policy may
change from time to time (see “Changes to Our Privacy Policy”). Your continued use
of the Website after we make changes to this privacy policy is deemed acceptance of
those changes, so please check this privacy policy periodically for updates.
Information We May Collect About You and How We Collect It
We may collect several types of information from and about users and performers (that
is, a self-employed person that produces, submits and publishes content on our Website
in order to offer such content for sale or a self-employed person offering interaction, for

example. responding to paid text messages from users and private chats via webcam
between users and the performer, all through our Website) of our Website, including
information:
              by which you may be personally identified, such as first and last name,
               mailing address, email address, billing information, IP or “Internet
               Protocol” addresses, demographics, passwords or other online contact
               information, telephone number, any other information the Website collects
               that is defined as personal or personally identifiable information under
               applicable law or other identifier by which you may be contacted online or
               offline (“personal information”);
              that is about you but individually does not identify you; or
              about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our
               Website, usage details (such as the web pages you visit, the links you
               click, and the searches you conduct on our Website), your browser type
               and language, access times, and the content of any undeleted cookies
               that your browser previously accepted from us.
We may collect this information:
              directly from you when you provide it to us,
              automatically, as you navigate through the site. Information collected
               automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information
               collected through cookies, web beacons or other tracking technologies, or
              from third parties, for example, other websites controlled by us or our
               affiliates, our business partners or other third parties.
All information we collect on this Website is subject to this Privacy Policy. By using the
Website, you consent to all actions taken by us with respect to your information in
compliance with this Privacy Policy.
Information You Provide To Us
The information we collect on or through our Website may include:
              Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This
               includes information provided at the time of registering to use our
               Website, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further
               services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest
               or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our
               Website.
              Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses),
               if you or any authorized service providers that perform certain services on
               our behalf (e.g. performer/customer support services) contact us.
              Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for
               research purposes.
              Details of transactions, if any, you may carry out through our Website and
               of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial
               information before placing an order through our Website.
              Your search queries on the Website.
                                              2

               We may also collect and store personal information about other people
                that you provide to us. If you use our Website to send others information
                that may interest them or messages through our system, we may store
                your personal information, and the personal information of each such
                recipient. Similarly, if you use our Website to upload, share or distribute
                content (including videos, comments or other submissions), and such
                content contains personal information about others, such information may
                be stored in order to allow for such uploading, sharing or distribution.
               When you access our Website from a mobile device like a tablet or
                phone, we may receive information about your location, your device,
                including one or more unique identifiers for your device, and your mobile
                carrier. We may use this information to provide you with location-based
                services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized
                content. Most devices allow you to turn off location services.
You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted”) on
public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties
(collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and
transmitted to others at your own risk. Although, we may limit access to certain pages,
please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we
cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to
share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your
User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.
Information We May Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies
As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data
collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing
actions and patterns, including:
               details of your visits to our Website, including any form of aggregate data,
                navigational data, tracking data, location data, click-stream data, or
                historical data, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the
                Website, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such
                information, log files and other communication data and the resources
                that you access and use on the Website; and
               information about your computer and internet connection, including your
                IP address, operating system and browser type and language, access
                times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously
                accepted from us. An IP, or “Internet Protocol”, address is a unique
                number associated with your computer that may be communicated to
                other computers and servers when you use the Internet. The information
                collected may include the domain name of your internet service provider,
                referral data (e.g., the address of the last page you visited prior to clicking
                through to the Website and the address of the exit page when you left our
                Website) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a
                Macintosh platform). We use this information to track how users are
                accessing and using the Website.
We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities
over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking).
                                               3

See “We use commercially reasonable safeguards (including physical, electronic and
procedural measures) to help safeguard the information that we collect about you from
unauthorized access and disclosure secure and take reasonable steps (such as
requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your
account. Furthermore, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal
information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we
use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your
system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from
gaining access to your personal information.
We want you to feel confident using our Website. However, no system can be
completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do
not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or
other communications will always remain secure.
Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information” below for information on
how you can opt out of behavioral tracking on this Website and how we respond to web
browser signals and other mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice about
behavioral tracking.
The information we collect automatically is statistical data and may include personal
information, or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in
other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver
a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:
              estimate our audience size and usage patterns;
              store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our
               Website according to your individual interests;
              speed up your searches; and
              recognize you when you return to our Website.
The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:
              Cookies (or browser cookies). Cookies are small text files that are
               stored in your web browser or downloaded to your device when you visit a
               website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each
               subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie.
               Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user’s
               device. Cookies might be used for the following purposes: (i) to enable
               certain functions; (ii) to provide analytics; (iii) to store your preferences;
               and (iv) to enable ad delivery and behavioral advertising.
               We currently use the following types of cookies:
                      Cookies that are strictly necessary: These are cookies that are
                       required for the operation of our Website. These include, for
                       example, cookies that enable a user to log into the members’ area
                       of our Website and to check if a user is allowed access to a
                       particular service or content.
                                              4

                      Analytical cookies: These cookies allow us to recognize and count
                       the number of users and to see how users use and explore our
                       Website. These cookies help us to improve our Website, for
                       example by ensuring that all users are able to find what they are
                       looking for easily.
                      Functionality cookies: We are always glad to see you back. This
                       type of cookies allows us to recognize you when you return to our
                       Website in order to greet you by name and to remember, for
                       example, your choice of language.
                      Targeting cookies: These cookies record the visit of a user on our
                       Website, the pages a user has visited and the links a user has
                       followed in order to enable us to make our Website more relevant
                       to the users’ interests. In addition, these cookies are used to
                       identify the websites and the marketing materials you are
                       accessing our Website from in order to target content (for
                       example, to automatically show you our Website according to your
                       language settings).
              We do not require that you accept cookies and you may withdraw your
              consent to our use of cookies at any time by adjusting your browser’s
              privacy settings. However, if you decline to accept cookies, some
              functionality on our Website may be disabled and you may be unable to
              access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your
              browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies
              when you direct your browser to our Website. Cookies can be either
              session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires
              automatically when you close your browser. A persistent cookie will
              remain until it expires or you delete your cookies. Expiration dates are set
              in the cookies themselves; some may expire after a few minutes while
              others may expire after multiple years.
             Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored
              objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your
              preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies
              are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser
              cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security
              settings for Flash cookies, see “We use commercially reasonable
              safeguards (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to
              help safeguard the information that we collect about you from
              unauthorized access and disclosure secure and take reasonable steps
              (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before
              granting you access to your account. Furthermore, only authorized
              employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may
              do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption
              in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your
              system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized
              persons from gaining access to your personal information.
We want you to feel confident using our Website. However, no system can be
completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do
                                              5

not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or
other communications will always remain secure.
             Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information”.
             Web Beacons. Pages of our the Website and our e-mails may contain
              small electronic files known as web beacons (also known as clear gifs,
              pixel tags, single-pixel gifs and web bugs) that are tiny graphics with a
              unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the
              online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies,
              which are stored on the user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are
              embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in an email) and are about the
              size of the period at the end of this sentence. Web beacons may be used
              to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited
              certain pages or opened an e-mail, to understand usage patterns and for
              other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of
              certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). We
              also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our
              site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.
             Device identifiers. When you use a mobile device like a tablet or phone
              to access our Website, we may access, collect, monitor, store on your
              device, or remotely store one or more “device identifiers”. Device
              identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or
              associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile
              device. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the
              device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating
              system or other software, or data sent to the device by the Website. A
              device identifier may deliver information to us or to a third party partner
              about how you browse and use the Website and may help others or us
              provide reports or personalized content and ads. Some features of the
              Website may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers
              is impaired or disabled.
             Metadata. Metadata is usually technical data that is associated with User
              Contributions. For example, Metadata can describe how, when and by
              whom a piece of User Contribution was collected and how that content is
              formatted. Users can add or may have Metadata added to their User
              Contribution including a hashtag, comments or other data. This makes
              your User Contribution more searchable by others and more interactive.
             Analytics Tools. We use analytics tools and other third party
              technologies, such as Google Analytics and DoubleClick Cookies, to
              collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user
              metrics when you use our Website. These tools and technologies collect
              and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses,
              device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior
              and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and
              purchase history, media access control address (MAC Address), mobile
              unique device identifiers, and other similar information. The third party
              analytics companies who collect information on our Website and other
              online products or services may combine the information collected with
              other information they have independently collected from other websites
                                              6

                or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities
                across their network of websites as well as online or mobile products and
                services. Many of these companies collect and use information under
                their own privacy policies. In addition to our use of technologies as
                described herein, we may permit certain third party companies to help us
                tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your
                use of our Website and to otherwise collect and use data about your use
                of our Website. For more information about this practice, please see the
                “Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies” section
                below.
                The information generated by Google Analytics and DoubleClick Cookies
                about your use of the Website (including your IP address) may be
                transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In
                case of activation of the IP anonymization, Google will
                truncate/anonymize the last octet of a particular IP address. Only in
                exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google
                servers in the USA. Google will use this information for the purpose of
                evaluating your use of the Website, compiling reports on Website activity
                and providing other services relating to Website activity and internet
                usage to the Website. Google will not associate your IP address with any
                other data held by Google.
                You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings
                on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be
                able to use the full functionality of this Website
                You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google
                advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by
                visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page.
                By downloading and installing the browser plug-in available at
                http://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin?hl=en, you can permanently
                opt out of the DoubleClick cookie. The plugin lets you keep your opt-out
                status even when you clear all cookies.
                Please note that on this Website, for some countries Google Analytics
                code may be supplemented by “gat._anonymizeIp();” to ensure an
                anonymized collection of IP addresses (so called IP-masking).
Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by
third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and
application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with
web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you
use our Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal
information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your
online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They
may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or
other targeted content.
We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If
you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should
                                                7

contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of
receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see “We use commercially
reasonable safeguards (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help
safeguard the information that we collect about you from unauthorized access and
disclosure secure and take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to
verify your identity before granting you access to your account. Furthermore, only
authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so
only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission
of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use
firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal
information.
We want you to feel confident using our Website. However, no system can be
completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do
not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or
other communications will always remain secure.
Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information”.
How We Use Your Information
In general, we use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us,
including any personal information:
               to present our Website and its contents to you;
               to provide you with information, products or services that you request
                from us;
               to manage your account and provide you with customer support;
               to provide you with notices about your account or subscription, including
                expiration and renewal notices;
               to notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services
                we offer or provide though it;
               to allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website;
               to perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our
                products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by
                others;
               to determine whether users of the Website are unique, or whether the
                same user is using the Website on multiple occasions;
               to track usage throughout various components of the Website (e.g.,
                tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Website,
                etc.);
               to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages
                viewed, demographic patterns, etc.;
               to communicate with you about products or services that may be of
                interest to you either from us, our affiliates or other third parties;
                                                8

                to develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests
                 on our Website and other sites;
                to verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and
                 sweepstakes;
                diagnose or fix technology problems;
                to enforce our terms and conditions;
                to manage our business;
                in any other way we may describe when you provide the information; or
                for any other purpose with your consent.
We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third parties’
services that may be of interest to you. For more information, see “We use commercially
reasonable safeguards (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help
safeguard the information that we collect about you from unauthorized access and
disclosure secure and take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to
verify your identity before granting you access to your account. Furthermore, only
authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so
only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission
of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use
firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal
information.
We want you to feel confident using our Website. However, no system can be
completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do
not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or
other communications will always remain secure.
Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information”.
We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display
advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose
your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or
otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its
target criteria.
Disclosure of Your Information
We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other
information we have collected about you or your activities on the Website or while using
our services.
We may transfer your information and process it outside your country of residence,
wherever the Website, its affiliates and service providers operate.
We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not
identify any individual, without restriction. We may combine non-personal information we
collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also
may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and
investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we
                                                 9

may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our Website and the most popular
features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal
information and may be used to develop content and services that we hope you and
other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising. We do not share
your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you
and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared:
               To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
               To our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our
                behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, processing credit card
                payments, risk and fraud detection and mitigation, providing customer
                service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales
                analysis, supporting our Website functionality, and supporting contests,
                sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our Website.
                These service providers may have access to personal information needed
                to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such
                information for any other purposes.
               To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture,
                restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some
                or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy,
                liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us
                about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
               To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have
                consented to these disclosures.
               To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
               For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
               With your consent.
We may also disclose your personal information:
               In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order
                or other judicial or administrative order, or a request for cooperation from
                a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise
                our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required
                by law (including responding to any government or regulatory request). In
                such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to
                us, in our sole discretion.
               When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to
                investigate, prevent, report or take other action regarding illegal activity,
                suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights,
                property, or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others;
                to maintain and protect the security and integrity of our Website or
                infrastructure; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law
                enforcement, government or regulatory agencies; or to enforce our
                Website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.
Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own
privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those
policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we
                                               10

have shared it with those third parties as described in this privacy policy. If you want to
learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the websites of those
third parties.
How We Store Your Information
The information that we collect about you, including personal information, may be stored
and processed in any country in which we, our affiliates or service providers maintain
facilities.
We may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information,
across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions
around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws
governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may
transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that
does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction.
By using the Website you consent to the transfer of information that we collect about
you, including personal information, to any country in which we, our affiliates or service
providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as
described in this privacy policy.
We use commercially reasonable safeguards (including physical, electronic and
procedural measures) to help safeguard the information that we collect about you from
unauthorized access and disclosure secure and take reasonable steps (such as
requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your
account. Furthermore, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal
information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we
use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your
system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from
gaining access to your personal information.
We want you to feel confident using our Website. However, no system can be
completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do
not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or
other communications will always remain secure.
Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to
us.
              You can choose not to provide us with certain personal information, but
               that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Website
               because such information may be required in order for you to register as
               a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest,
               promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other
               transactions on our Website.
              You may, at any time, update, correct, or delete certain personal
               information that you have provided to us by contacting us at the email
               address provided at the end of this privacy policy.
              You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to
               alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage
               your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s
                                            11

               website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of
               the Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
              You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google
               advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by
               visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page.
              You may permanently opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by downloading
               and installing the browser plug-in available at Google Analytics opt-out
               page. The plugin lets you keep your opt-out status even when you clear
               all cookies.
              When you register on our Website, you may be given a choice as to
               whether you want to receive email messages, newsletters or both about
               product updates, improvements, special offers, or containing special
               distributions of content by us. If you no longer want to receive commercial
               or promotional emails or newsletters from us, you will need to avail
               yourself of the unsubscribe mechanism set out in the applicable
               communication. It may take up to seven days for us to process an opt-out
               request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-
               mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative
               notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of
               receiving them. Please note that opting out of receipt of promotional email
               communications will only affect future activities or communications from
               us. If we have already provided your information to a third party before
               you have changed your preferences or updated your information, you
               may have to change you preferences directly with that third party.
              If you submit personal information, you may delete your account with us
               at any time. If you delete your account, your personal information and any
               and all other account related information including, but not limited to, user
               profile data, sharing data and any other data, or content specifically
               associated with your account will no longer be accessible by you. After
               deleting your account, if you choose to have an account with us in the
               future, you will have to sign up for a new account as none of the
               information you previously provided or saved within your account will
               have been saved.
              You can disable the location services on your mobile device or tablet.
               Most likely, these controls are located in the device's settings menu. If you
               have questions about how to disable your device's location services, we
               recommend you contact your mobile service carrier or your device
               manufacturer.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural
measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and
disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal
information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we
use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your
system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from
gaining access to your personal information.
                                             12

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given
you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website,
you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your
password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public
areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas
may be viewed by any user of the Website.
We want you to feel confident using our Website. However, no system can be
completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do
not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or
other communications would always remain secure. Users should also take care with
how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending
personal information through insecure email. We are not responsible for circumvention of
any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.
User Contributions
We may provide areas on our Website where you can post information about yourself
and others and communicate with others, upload content (e.g., pictures, videos, audio
files, etc.), and post comments or reviews of content found on the Website. Such
postings are governed by our terms of use found at https://cdn1-l-ha-
e11.mdhcdn.com/u/TermsofUse_en.pdf. If you use a forum, blog, channel, bulletin
board, chat room, user commenting features, or other interactive sharing or social
features that may be offered through our Website, you should be aware that any
personal information you submit, display, or publish there is considered publicly available
and can be read, collected, used, and disclosed by other users of those features, by us,
and other third parties without restriction, except to the extent limited access features are
available, if any. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when
searches are executed on the subject of your posting. If you post your email address,
you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or
what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you
to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you
have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information. To
request removal of your personal information from our blog, sharing service or
community forum, for example, send us an e-mail at support@MyDirtyHobby.com. In
some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we
will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Accessing and Correcting Your Information
You may, at any time, send us an e-mail at support@MyDirtyHobby.com to request
access to, correct or delete certain personal information that you have provided to us,
except personal information or data that is necessary for administration purposes or for
fraud prevention measures. We cannot delete your personal information except by also
deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if
we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the
information to be incorrect.
If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User
Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been
copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided
on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our terms of use found at
https://cdn1-l-ha-e11.mdhcdn.com/u/TermsofUse_en.pdf.
                                              13

Financial Information
Any financial data that you have provided to us will only be shared with the Website's
third party processors in order to initiate and complete any orders placed on your
account. All credit card transactions and such are processed with industry standard
encryption through third party processors who only use your information for that purpose.
All financial data and information shall be considered private information and will not be
shared by the Website with third parties except with your authorization or when
necessary to carry out all and any transactions requested by the user with the
understanding that such transactions may be subject to rules, terms, conditions and
policies of a third party. All such information provided to a third party and all transactions
are not governed by this privacy policy. All such information provided to a third party is
subject to their terms and conditions.
Third Party Login Functionality
We may permit users with accounts on certain third party services, including but not
limited to, social networking, search, sharing, and other services delivered by third
parties, to bypass the standard applicable registration process. If you connect through an
authorized third party service, you will be able to use your third party login information to
log in to your account or access our content and Website. We are not responsible for the
sharing, posting, commenting, or other content and information gathering practices of
any third party services that may be triggered by using these third party login services.
Please review their terms of service and privacy policies carefully before using third party
login functionality to access our Website.
By using any third party services to log in to your account or access our Website, you
permit us to access, store and use all information related to your third party account that
may be accessible to us through the third party service, including through its application
programming interface (API), pursuant to this privacy policy.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We may modify or revise our privacy policy from time to time in our sole discretion and
you agree to be bound by such modifications or revisions. Although we may attempt to
notify you when major changes are made to this privacy policy, you are expected to
periodically review the most up-to-date version found at https://cdn1-l-ha-
e11.mdhcdn.com/u/privacypolicy_en.pdf, so you are aware of any changes, as they are
binding on you.
If we change anything in our privacy policy, the date of change will be reflected in the
“last modified date”. You agree that you will periodically review this privacy policy and
refresh the page when doing so. You agree to note the date of the last revision to our
privacy policy. If the “last modified” date is unchanged from the last time you reviewed
our privacy policy, then it is unchanged. On the other hand, if the date has changed, then
there have been changes, and you agree to re-review our privacy policy, and you agree
to the new ones.
All changes are effective immediately when we post them, and apply to all access to and
use of the Website thereafter. The updated version of our privacy policy supersedes any
prior versions immediately upon being posted, and the prior version(s) shall have no
continuing legal effect. If you do not review new terms as posted, then you agree that
you have waived your right to do so, and you are therefore bound by the updated
conditions, even if you failed to review the new ones. You are on notice of changes, and
your failure to review the amended terms is your own omission. By continuing to use the
                                              14

Website subsequent to us making available an amended version of our privacy policy,
you thereby acknowledge, agree to and consent to such amendment.
Enforcement
We regularly review our compliance with this privacy policy. Please feel free to direct any
questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or our treatment of personal
information by contacting us through this Website at support@MyDirtyHobby.com. When
we receive a formal written complaint, it is our policy to contact the complaining party
regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory
authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints
regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved by an individual and us.
No Rights of Third Parties
This privacy policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require
disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Website.
Our Policy Towards Children
Our Website is not directed to children. If you become aware that your child has provided
us with personal information, please contact us at support@MyDirtyHobby.com. We do
not knowingly collect personal information from children. If we become aware that a child
has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information
and terminate the child’s account.
No Error Free Performance
We do not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use
reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective
action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. We shall not be
liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this privacy policy.
The laws of Cyprus shall, to the extent applicable, govern this privacy policy.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our information-handling practices,
please contact us at support@MyDirtyHobby.com.
                                              15
